medicalmarijuanaexchange.com 2015-06-15

# Privacy Policy - Medical Marijuana Exchange

## Privacy Policy 

 **Privacy Policy**

We love our community at The Medical Marijuana Exchange , We are committed to upholding the highest standard when it comes to our privacy practices. It’s important to us that you’re comfortable on The Medical Marijuana Exchange , so we provide options for you to control how much information you share and your communication preferences. We use secure technologies and follow best practices, which allows us to provide responsible privacy practices. We believe in being transparent in our services and about our practices, which is why we provide a detailed Privacy Policy to explain how we gather, use, and protect your information. 

By visiting this website, you are accepting the terms of this Privacy Policy. Any external links to other websites are clearly identifiable as such, and we are not responsible for the content or the privacy policies of these other websites.

 **Scope**

This page highlights key points about the information The Medical Marijuana Exchange

 collects or receives about you, how it is used, and your choices.

 **Information Collected or Received**

The Medical Marijuana Exchange  requires a member to provide a valid email address and choose a username connected with your site activity. Depending on the services you choose, additional information may be collected, for example: billing or payment information, a telephone number, or a physical address.

You may optionally choose to provide your full name and other personal information (such as birthday, gender, location) to be publicly displayed.

You may connect to The Medical Marijuana Exchange  with an external application, in which case The Medical Marijuana Exchange may receive some information from that other service.

We use browser cookies, clear gifs, log files, and flash cookies to help understand how people interact with our site and services, in order to provide a better experience.

 **Uses**

We use the information which we gather from our users to provide and improve our services, and to communicate with you.

The Medical Marijuana Exchange  will not sell or disclose your personal information to third parties without your explicit consent, except as specified in our Privacy Policy.

 **Choices**

Members may review and change your information in your account settings, and you may remove certain optional pieces of information.

You may opt-out of receiving certain types of communications from The Medical Marijuana Exchange  in your account settings.

You may disable cookies in your web browser.

 **Important Information**

 If you have questions or concerns regarding our privacy policy or practices, please contact us at info@medicalmarijuanaexchange.com

We’ll communicate when we make changes to our Privacy Policy, and we’ll update the revision date above.
